https://www.cronisraelsandstark.com/privacy-policy/

Main MenuCloseFirm OverviewCriminal Case ProcessPractice AreasDomestic ViolenceAnnoying Phone CallsBatterers’ Intervention ProgramChild AbuseChild EndangermentCourt ProcessCriminal ThreatsDefensesDomestic Violence FAQDomestic Violence PenaltiesDV Claims For Child CustodyElder AbuseFalse ImprisonmentFirearmsFirst Domestic ViolenceIntimidationProbationProtective OrdersReduced ChargesRestraining OrdersSame Sex Domestic ViolenceSentencingSpousal AbuseStalkingVictim RestitutionViolation of Restraining OrderDrug CrimesCocaineConspiracyDrug Cultivation/ Grow HouseDrug Diversion ProgramDrug ParaphernaliaDrug SalesFederal Drug CrimesForging or Altering a PrescriptionHeroinManufacturing a Controlled SubstanceMarijuana CrimesMarijuana SalesMethamphetaminePossession of DrugsPossession of MethPossession of Meth for SalePrescription DrugsPrescription FraudDUIDUI OverviewDUI Defense StrategiesDMV HearingDUI Court ProcessField Sobriety TestsBlood and Breath TestsAlcohol Test RefusalsSobriety CheckpointsOut of State DriversFelony DUIFelony Hit and RunDUI Involving AccidentsDrugs And DUIUnderage DUIDUI PenaltiesPrior DUI ConvictionsVehicular ManslaughterWatson DUI MurderSex CrimesChild MolestationChild PornographyContinuous Sexual Abuse of a ChildHuman TraffickingIndecent ExposureLewd Acts with a MinorLewd & Lascivious BatteryLewd & Lascivious MolestationLoitering for ProstitutionOral Copulation with a MinorPimping and PanderingProstitution & SolicitationRevenge PornSending Harmful Matter to Seduce a MinorSex Offender RegistrationSexual Battery and RapeStatutory RapeTheft and FraudAuto BurglaryBurglaryDefrauding an InnkeeperForgeryGrand TheftIdentity TheftInsurance FraudMoney LaunderingOperating a Chop ShopOrganized FraudPetty Theft with a PriorReceiving Stolen PropertyShoplifting/petty theftWriting or Passing Bad ChecksViolent CrimesAssault with Deadly WeaponAssault/Aggravated AssaultAttempted MurderAssault on a Police OfficerAssault on a Public OfficialBattery/Aggravated BatteryBattery Causing Serious Bodily InjuryCarjackingKidnapping During a CarjackingChild AbuseFalse Imprisonment of a HostageFirearm OffensesKidnappingManslaughterMurderRobbery / BurglaryVoluntary ManslaughterFederal CrimesCredit Card FraudHealth Care FraudMail FraudMedicare FraudMortgage FraudRICOWeapons OffensesWhite Collar CrimesWire FraudJuvenile CrimesPossession of AlcoholSuspended LicenseDrug PossessionDependency ProceedingsJoyridingJuvenile Law AppealsSealing Juvenile RecordsCrimes at SchoolJuvenile Sex CrimesVandalismOther OffensesAnimal Abuse and CrueltyCarrying a Concealed WeaponContributing to Delinquency of a MinorCriminal AppealsDestroy or Conceal EvidenceDisorderly ConductDisturbing the PeaceDriving on a Suspended LicenseDrunk in PublicEvading ArrestExpungementsExtraditionsFalse Statements to PoliceFiling a False DocumentForfeituresFraudulent ConveyanceHit and RunObstruction of JusticePossession of Fake Driver’s LicenseProbation ViolationsReckless DrivingRepresenting High Profile CasesResisting ArrestSolicitation to Commit a CrimeAttorney ProfilesPhilip D. IsraelsSam IsraelsSteven M. CronEdward C. StarkCase ResultsTestimonialsFAQBlogNewsContact UsPrivacy PolicyWe recognize that you may be concerned about our use and disclosure of your personal information. Your privacy is very important to us, and the following will inform you of the information that we, Cron, Israels & Stark, may collect from you, and how it is used. By using our website, www.cronisraelsandstark.com, you are accepting the practices described in this policy.Information CollectionWe may collect non-personal information, such as a domain name and IP Address. The domain name and IP address reveals nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We may also collect information about the type of Internet browser you are using, operating system, what brought you to our Website, as well as which of our Web pages you have accessed.Additionally, if you communicate with us regarding our Website or our services, we will collect any information that you provide to us in any such communication.We may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.Information UseWe use the collected information primarily for our own internal purposes, such as providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving our services and Website, fulfilling requests for information, and providing customer support.SecurityWe follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.If we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.CookiesWe use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.SharingWe will not sell or otherwise provide the information we collect to outside third parties for the purpose of direct or indirect mass email marketing.We will disclose personal information and/or an IP address, when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities and conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on our companyProtect and defend the rights or property of our Website and related propertiesIdentify persons who may be violating the law, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing our Website or its related propertiesPlease keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online – for example through e-mail, discussion boards, or elsewhere – that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.LinksThis Website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.Surveys & ContestsFrom time-to-time our site may request information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.ConsentBy using this Website, you consent to the collection and use of information as specified above. If we make changes to our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page. Please review this page frequently to remain up-to-date with the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. You must review the new Privacy Policy carefully to make sure you understand our practices and procedures.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (310) 451-9888 or via mail Attn: Privacy Officer, 1541 Ocean Avenue, Suite 200, Santa Monica, CA 91401.Practice AreasDomestic ViolenceAnnoying Phone CallsBatterers’ Intervention ProgramChild AbuseChild EndangermentCourt ProcessCriminal ThreatsDefensesDomestic Violence FAQDomestic Violence PenaltiesDV Claims For Child CustodyElder AbuseFalse ImprisonmentFirearmsFirst Domestic ViolenceIntimidationProbationProtective OrdersReduced ChargesRestraining OrdersSame Sex Domestic ViolenceSentencingSpousal AbuseStalkingVictim RestitutionViolation of Restraining OrderDrug CrimesCocaineConspiracyDrug Cultivation/ Grow HouseDrug Diversion ProgramDrug ParaphernaliaDrug SalesFederal Drug CrimesForging or Altering a PrescriptionHeroinManufacturing a Controlled SubstanceMarijuana CrimesMarijuana SalesMethamphetaminePossession of DrugsPossession of MethPossession of Meth for SalePrescription DrugsPrescription FraudDUIDUI OverviewDUI Defense StrategiesDMV HearingDUI Court ProcessField Sobriety TestsBlood and Breath TestsAlcohol Test RefusalsSobriety CheckpointsOut of State DriversFelony DUIFelony Hit and RunDUI Involving AccidentsDrugs And DUIUnderage DUIDUI PenaltiesPrior DUI ConvictionsVehicular ManslaughterWatson DUI MurderTheft and FraudAuto BurglaryBurglaryDefrauding an InnkeeperForgeryGrand TheftIdentity TheftInsurance FraudMoney LaunderingOperating a Chop ShopOrganized FraudPetty Theft with a PriorReceiving Stolen PropertyShoplifting/petty theftWriting or Passing Bad ChecksViolent CrimesAssault with Deadly WeaponAssault/Aggravated AssaultAssault on a Police OfficerAssault on a Public OfficialAttempted MurderBattery/Aggravated BatteryBattery Causing Serious Bodily InjuryCarjackingChild AbuseFalse Imprisonment of a HostageFirearm OffensesKidnappingKidnapping During a CarjackingManslaughterMurderRobbery / BurglaryVoluntary ManslaughterFederal CrimesCredit Card FraudHealth Care FraudMail FraudMedicare FraudMortgage FraudRICOWeapons OffensesWhite Collar CrimesWire FraudJuvenile CrimesPossession of AlcoholSuspended LicenseDrug PossessionDependency ProceedingsJoyridingJuvenile Law AppealsSealing Juvenile RecordsCrimes at SchoolJuvenile Sex CrimesVandalismSex CrimesChild MolestationChild PornographyContinuous Sexual Abuse of a ChildHuman TraffickingIndecent ExposureLewd Acts with a MinorLewd & Lascivious BatteryLewd & Lascivious MolestationLoitering for ProstitutionOral Copulation with a MinorPimping and PanderingProstitution & SolicitationRevenge PornSending Harmful Matter to Seduce a MinorSex Offender RegistrationSexual Battery and RapeStatutory RapeOther OffensesAnimal Abuse and CrueltyCarrying a Concealed WeaponContributing to Delinquency of a MinorCriminal AppealsDestroy or Conceal EvidenceDisorderly ConductDisturbing the PeaceDrunk in PublicEvading ArrestExpungementsExtraditionsFalse Statements to PoliceFiling a False DocumentForfeituresFraudulent ConveyanceHit and RunObstruction of JusticePossession of Fake Driver’s LicenseProbation ViolationsRepresenting High Profile CasesResisting ArrestSolicitation to Commit a Crime
